I was scared brother.
I thought it was Bradesco's.
I have 1 idea here that works out Dude it's going to be time
I have 1 idea but I don't see it here at the post office
Cara so I'm going to the stationery store.
Maybe this will work.
beauty.
Bye bro it's good yesterday I saw your video bro congratulations.
See what's your name?
My name is Ivan.
I was scared brother.
I thought it was Bradesco's.
Ha ha ha ô mano congratulations vei ô brigadão mano ah that from the time that
this mano brother 1 hug here Cara tamo close man I'm going to that guy see
that I give him a gift mano caraca brother valeuzão mano but I just don't accept
money you accept what not because it's the challenge you.
Want to give me a real gift?
I like guys coffee.
I was kidnapped here on the street doing things and look where I am.
Are you calling me for some coffee?
Because you saw my video.
Thanks.
Saw my bro and the guy came to recognize me.
I went to have some coffee.
It's on to finding a store that sells exactly what I'm looking for.
It gives 1 discount,
it doesn't work on pix.
No thanks,
young man.
It was worth coming to this little shop.
Now I need to buy my raw material to come up with my idea.
I'm investing a gram if it doesn't work out.
It screwed.
I bought all the things.
That was day four there was no sale but he had investment.
Wait until tomorrow and I'll get the content ready for you.
Tamo together.